我来这儿  已经上了十次厕所了
That's like the 10th time I've peed since I've been here.
你也跟我们说了十次了
It's also, like, the 10th time you've told us. Ha, ha.
抱歉  你们一定听烦了
Yeah, oh, I'm sorry, it must be hard to hear.
我告诉你们  三个宝宝在你的膀胱上
I'll tell you, it's a lot easier having three babies playing...
蹦蹦跳跳还比较好玩
...Bringing in the Noise, Bringing in da Funk on your bladder!
我真是受够怀孕了
I am so sick of being pregnant.
我唯一的乐趣来自咖啡
The only happiness I get is from a cup of coffee...
低咖啡因的  因为我怀孕了
...which of course is decaf because, oh, I'm pregnant. Heh.
菲比  要吃饼干吗
Pheebs, you want a cookie?
谢谢你
Thank you so much.
菲比  亲爱的  你的情绪起伏还好吗
So, uh, Pheebs, honey, how are those mood swings coming?
我还没有这个困扰
I haven't really had any yet.
老友记  第四季  第22集  史上最差伴郎
Friends  S04E22  The One With The Worst Best Man Ever
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
嘿  两位  嘿
Hey, guys. Hey.
好了  这就是戒指
All right. Here's the ring.
我愿意  我愿意  千百个愿意
Yes, yes. A thousand times, yes.
单身派对有想法了吗
So, uh, any ideas for the bachelor party?
找人托管戒指办派对前
Before you start handing out rings and planning bachelor parties...
你不应该先选个伴郎吗
...don't you have to decide who your best man's gonna be?
真尴尬   尴尬  尴尬
Oh, it's awkward. It's awkward, it's awkward.
我已经找钱德了
I sort of already asked Chandler.
什么  你上次结婚他就当过了
What? He got to do it at your first wedding.
乔伊  我以为你会了解  我们认识也比较久了
Joey, I figured you'd understand. I've known him a lot longer.
拜托啦  罗斯  我没有兄弟  我永远都没有机会了
Come on, Ross. I don't have any brothers. I'm never gonna get to be a best man.
你可以当我的伴郎啊
You can be the best man when I get married.
我没机会了啦
I'm never gonna get to be a best man.
等一下  等一下
Wait, wait.
我让你当两次  你一次也不让我当
So you get to be my best man twice, and I don't get to be yours at all?
你当然可以当我的伴郎
Oh, no. Yeah, of course, you can be my best man.
那我呢  你说我可以当
What about me? You just said I could.
我又没有要结婚
I'm not even getting married!
那是科幻小说要挑战的题材
Okay, this is a question for science-fiction writers.
不敢相信你居然不找我
I can't believe you're not picking me.
你怎么能不找我  我又没要
Hey, how could it not be me? I'm not even...
我又没要  好了  够了
I'm not even... All right, you know what? That's it.
从现在起  乔伊  你当我的伴郎
From now on, Joey I want you to be my best man.
帅  不过你真的很烂
Yes. Shame about you, though.
别闹  怎么了
Stop it. What?
有个宝宝在踢
One of the babies is kicking.
那不是好事吗  不是踢我
I thought that was a good thing. It's not kicking me.
是踢另一个宝宝
It's kicking one of the other babies.
别逼我进去
Oh. Don't make me come in there!
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
有大碗可以借我吗
Do you guys have, like, a big bowl I can borrow?
柜子下面正好有一个
Yeah, there's one right under the cabinet.
谢谢  干嘛
Thanks. Why do you need it?
我们明天要开派对  稍后见
Oh, we're having a party tomorrow night. Later.
嗨  你们有打算要邀请我们吗
Hey, hey. Are you planning on inviting us?
没有  稍后见
No. No, no. Later.
嘿  崔比亚尼  给我滚回来
Hey, get your ass back here, Tribbiani!
荷尔蒙
Hormones.
菲比的意思是
What Phoebe meant was...
你们开派对怎么不邀请我们
...how come you're having a party and we're not invited?
啊  那是罗斯的单身派对
Oh. It's Ross' bachelor party.
所以呢  你们是单身吗
So? Are you bachelors?
不是  那你们是脱衣舞娘吗
No. Are you strippers?
不是  那就对了  抱歉
No. Then you're not invited.
也行  那你们也别想参加我们的派对
All right, fine. You're not invited to the party that we're gonna have either.
什么派对
Oh, what party?
那个
Well, um...
菲比的送礼会
The baby shower for Phoebe.
送礼会
Baby shower?
听起来就不想参加  稍后见
Wow. That so doesn't sound like something I want to do. Later.
你们居然要帮我办派对
I can't believe I'm going to have a party!
太棒了  派对啊
Ha, ha. That's so great. A party!
耶
Yay! Ha, ha.
我也不知道怎么了
I don't know why. Oh.
在酒方面我的计划是
This is what I got going for the party so far liquor-wise.
买大堆酒  很好  很好
Get a lot of liquor. Great. Great.
至于邀请名单有你  我  钱德
Okay, now, uh, in terms of the invite list, obviously I got you, me and Chandler.
我也会请阿甘  因为我们讨论得很大声
And I'm invite Gunther because, well, we've been talking pretty loud.
我会去的
I'll be there.
听好  派对是为你办的
Oh, listen. I know it's your party...
但我想限制博物馆怪脚的人数
...but I'd really like to limit the number of museum geeks that are gonna be there.
那就别找人类学家  好吧
Yeah. Tell you what. Let's not invite any anthropologists, okay?
只找搞恐龙的就行
Just the dinosaur dudes.
好  还得买半打汽水酒
Okay, we'll need a six-pack of Zima.
嗨  伙计们  你们在干嘛
Hey, guys, what are you doing?
跟我的伴郎筹划我的单身派对啊
Oh, just planning my bachelor party with my best man.
祝你们办得比上次好
Yeah, well, good luck trying to top the last one.
这不难  因为这次不会在
I don't think it's gonna be that difficult, considering this one won't take place...
必胜客的地下室举办了
...in the basement of a Pizza Hut. Heh.
我是罗斯  我是罗斯
Oh, I'm Ross, I'm Ross.
必胜客配不上我  配不上我
I'm too good for the Hut. I'm too good for the Hut.
我得去接班了  看样子没问题
Look, I gotta go pick up Ben. Uh, everything so far sounds great, Joey.
总之记住  不要太疯了
Just remember, keep it on the mellow side, okay?
大家一起聚一聚打打牌
Just a couple guys hanging out playing poker.
不要找脱衣舞娘  好吗  没问题
No strippers or anything, okay? You got it.
待会见
Okay, see you later. Yeah.
好好办不能疯的派对吧
Ha, ha. Have fun planning your mellow party.
会有脱衣舞娘
There's gonna be strippers there.
他没说不要脱衣舞娘啊
He didn't say anything about no strippers.
他刚刚才说不要的  我当作没听到
He just said, "No strippers." Oh. I chose not to hear that.
你看我买了什么   买了什么
Look what I got, look what I got, look what I got.
居然有这种童装
Can you believe they made these for little people?
给乡下小孩穿的
Aw. Little Village People.
好  你看这件  我最喜欢这件
Aw, okay. Look at this one. This is my favorite.
太可爱了
Oh, that is so sweet.
菲比一定会很喜欢打扮他们
Phoebe's gonna love dressing them in these.
但到时候  替他们打扮的不是她
Huh. Except, uh, Phoebe's not gonna be the one who gets to dress them.
因为她不能把宝宝留着
I guess she's not gonna get to keep the babies.
天哪  这真是最今人沮丧的送礼会
Oh, my God, we are throwing the most depressing baby shower ever!
等等  除非我们送她产后可以用的礼物
Wait a minute. Unless we give her all gifts that she can use...
像普通咖徘  龙舌兰酒
...after she's done being pregnant. Like, um, regular coffee. Tequila.
还有她一直想要的皮裤
Oh, and somebody can get her those leather pants she's always wanted.
她一定会很高兴
Oh, she's gonna love that.
这是什么玩意儿
What the hell is this?
送我两个月后才能用的礼物
What, did you actually thought it'd make me feel better?
我的心情会好吗
To give me something I can't even use for another two months?
真是烂透了
This sucks! Oh!
好了  下个礼物呢
All right, what's my next present?
我们都没带
I don't have anything.
对了  那个脱衣舞娘
Hey, listen, man, about the stripper...
怎样  叫得好
Yeah? Good call.
请注意  请注意
A little announcement. A little announcement.
我决定我的伴郎  是我最要好的朋友阿甘
I've decided that my best man is my best friend Gunther.
我姓什么
What's my last name?
中央咖啡厅
Central Perk?
谢谢你没娶瑞秋
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
哦等等  阿甘  记得拿衣服
Oh-whoa-wait, Gunther. Don't forget your shirt.
嘿  那是什么
Hey. Hey, what are those?
派对小赠品   你看
Little party favors. Check it out.
（罗斯盖勒单身派对 1998)
"Ross Geller, Bachelor Bash 1998"
（伴郎 乔伊崔比亚尼）
"Best Man Joey Tribbiani"
好了  请注意
Okay, little announcement.
我的伴郎人选还空着呢
I just want everybody to know the position of my best man is still open.
新娘人选也是
And, uh, you know, so is the position of the bride.
很好
Great.
你真有一套  你的脖子沾到辣椒了
Smooth, man. Yeah. You got some chili on your neck.
谢谢大家   今晚很愉快
Well, I just want to say thanks, everyone. This was great.
星期一早上见
Okay? And hey, I'll see you guys Monday morning.
乔伊  谢了  别忘了拿衣服
Thanks, Joey. Oh, hey. Don't forget your shirt.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
好了  博物馆怪胎   派对结束了
Ahem. Okay. Hey, museum geeks. Party's over.
跟漂亮小姐说再见  快点
Okay, wave bye-bye to the nice lady. There you go.
回爸妈的地下室去
Back to your parents' basement. All right.
出来吧  来  出来  这里来
Come on, boys, come on out. Here you go.
好可爱
Oh. Look at the birdies.
是你养的  对
Are those yours? Yeah.
我不知道还可以养鸡鸭当宠物
Wow, I didn't know they let you keep chickens and ducks as pets?
对  我把鸭子训练得很好
Oh, yeah, yeah. And I got the duck totally trained too.
你看  盯着墙壁
Watch this. Stare at the wall.
停着不动
Hardly move.
白白的
Be white.
你真行
You are really good at that.
今晚很愉快
Oh. So I had fun tonight.
派对办得很棒
You throw one hell of a party.
谢了 很高兴认识你
Thanks, thanks. Yeah, it was great meeting you.
要是我有朋友要结婚  或是过生日  过星期二
And listen, if any of my friends ever get married or have a birthday or a Tuesday...
那就太好了
Yeah, that'd be great. Okay. Ha, ha.
那就再见了
So, I guess, um, good night.
除非你  想留下来
Oh, unless you, uh... Unless you want to hang around.
是吗  对啊  你可以跟我的鸭子玩
Yeah? Yeah. I'll let you play with my duck.
嘿
Hey...
跳脱衣舞的
Stripper.
舞娘把戒指偷走了
The stripper stole the ring!
钱德  起床  舞娘把戒指偷走了
Chandler, get up, get up! The stripper stole the ring!
什么  戒指被偷了
What? The ring is gone!
别闹  给我一分钟先让我清醒一下
Oh. Okay, just, like, give me a minute to wake up for this.
你把戒指弄丢了  你是最烂的伴郎
You lost the ring. You're the worst best man ever.
一点都不好笑  怎么办
Dude, this isn't funny. What am I gonna do?
昨晚我去睡觉  一切正常
I go to sleep last night, everything's cool.
等我醒来  舞娘不见了  戒指也不见了
I wake up this morning, the stripper's gone, and the ring is gone!
你跟她上床了  废话
You slept with the stripper? Of course!
你们两个
Hi, guys.
嗨  菲比
Hi, Phoebe.
我想说声抱歉  我昨天在送礼会上
Ahem. I wanted to apologize if I, you know, seemed a tad edgy yesterday...
似乎凶了点
...at my shower.
没事  都是荷尔蒙在作怪
You know, it's just the hormones. You know?
别这样  我们  对啊  荷尔蒙嘛
No, we... Hormones. Yeah. Hormones.
谢谢你们  你们真有心
Anyway, I just wanted to say thank you. It was just... It was so sweet.
真有心
Oh, okay. So sweet.
你似乎好多了
Yeah. Wow, you seem to be doing much better.
太好了  你现在怎样  很好
That's great. How are things going? Good.
可是  最近的注意力都在我自己身上
No, but... Okay, it feels like everything's been about me lately.
你们怎么呢
So, what's happening with you?
我们正在说  我不去参加罗斯的婚礼
Oh. Well, actually, we were just talking about me not going to Ross' wedding.
曾经有那段过往
Oh. It just might be too hard...
我可能很难面对现实
...given the history and all that.
这让我想起当年流落街头时
Wow, this reminds me of the time when I was, um, living on the street.
有人说我陪他上床就请我吃饭
And this guy offered to buy me food if I slept with him.
这两件事哪里像啊
Well, how is this like that?
我想想  的确不像
Well, let's see. It's not really like that.
因为那样才算是问题
Because, you see, that was an actual problem.
你这只是高中女生无病呻吟
And, uh, yours is just, like, a bunch of high-school crap...
没人在乎的
...that nobody really gives... Yeah.
抱歉  我只是
Well, I'm sorry. I just thought...
泪眼攻势来了
All right, here come the waterworks.
我已经完全没辙了
Oh. I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我打给中介站  他们不管
I called the company that sent her, and they don't care.
我打119又被对方吼骂
And I called 911 and they yelled at me.
都这样了  还不能算紧急事件吗
If this isn't an emergency, then what is?
嘿  两位  嘿
Hey, guys. Hey.
谢谢你  昨晚派对办得很棒
I just wanted to thank you for last night. What a great party.
博物馆那伙人玩得很爽
And the guys from work had a blast.
其中有一个没参加过单身派对
You know, one of them had never been to a bachelor party before.
另一个没参加过任何派对  所以
Yeah, and another one had never been to a party before, so...
那个  结婚戒指
So, uh, hey, that wedding ring, huh?
可真漂亮  漂亮吧
Man, that is nice. Yeah. Yeah, right?
我也想给自己买一只
Yeah, I was thinking I might pick one of those babies up for myself.
去哪里能买得到啊
Where might one get one of those?
那只戒指  我奶奶刚来到这个国家时
That ring, when my grandmother first came to this country...
全身上下只有那只戒指  和一小包衣服
...that ring and the clothes on her back were all she had with her.
所以那只戒指可以说是独一无二
So you might say that the ring is irreplaceable.
显然  它是我家的传家宝
Oh, absolutely. It's been in my family for generations.
每个新娘戴上它  都能预示着幸福到老
And every bride who's worn it has lived a long and happy life.
所以简直算是一只魔戒
So you might say it's a magic ring.
被脱衣舞娘偷了
Yeah, the stripper stole it.
我的戒指  我的结婚戒指
My ring? My wedding ring?
脱衣舞娘偷了我的结婚戒指
The stripper stole my wedding ring?
怎么  怎么会这样
How? How could this happen?
原因就在于你说了 "乔伊  你来当我的伴郎吧"
Well, I think it all started when you said, "Hey, Joey, why don't you be my best man."
好  我来报警
All right, all right. Fine. I'm gonna call the cops.
我搞砸了  你也用不着报警抓我啊
Dude, I screwed up. You don't have to turn me in.
不是抓你  是抓那个舞娘  我试过了
Not on you, on the stripper. Oh, yeah, well, I already did that.
他们说等侦破完所有谋杀案再说
They said they're gonna look into it right after they solve all the murders...
那好  就找舞娘中介站
Okay, we'll call the company that sent her.
我也试过了
I did that too.
他们不肯透露她的真名或电话
They wouldn't give me her name or number.
他们说我再打去  就要报警
They said if I bother them again, they'd call the police.
我说  "你去报警啊  就说我掉了一只戒指"
I said, "You talk to the police, you tell them I'm missing a ring."
乔伊  你说说  一点办法也没有了
So, what, Joey? What are you telling me? That there's nothing we can do?
怎么会这样  罗斯  我真的很抱歉
How could this happen? Look, Ross, I am so, so sorry.
这样  我们何不再叫她一次
Well, what if we just, uh, called her...
用假名召她  然后去我的办公室
...used a fake name and had her come to my office?
好像不赖  但我们只能找戒指
Oh, that sounds like fun, but we got a ring to find!
菲比  你的茶
Here's your tea, Phoebe.
感觉真好
Mm. It's so good.
谢谢  真好心
Oh, thanks. That's sweet.
那就好  你喜欢就好
Good. So glad you like it.
怎么了
Oh. What?
什么  茶是她泡的
What? She made the tea.
不是  我刚才阵痛了
No, I think I just had a contraction.
什么  天哪
You what? My God.
几分钟前就有一次
Yeah, I thought I felt one a couple minutes ago.
这次绝对错不了  你不能在这里生
And now I know that definitely was one. Well, you can't have the baby here!
男生搬走之后我还没消毒
I haven't sterilized the apartment since the guys moved out!
没事  别怕
It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
你懂什么  我来烧水  撕床单
You know what? It's okay. I'm gonna boil some water and just rip up some sheets.
别紧张  可能是假性阵痛
Ow, it's all right. It's probably false labor.
他们说  接近预产期会这样  赶快
They said that, that can happen near the end. So just...
去拿书来  瑞秋  拿书来
Somebody get the book. Rachel, get the book.
书  好  好
The book. Okay. Okay. Here.
《圣经》啊   我哪懂啊
The Bible? I don't know!
好  很好  就这样
All right. Okay, okay. This is great.
钱德  你站到桌子后面
Uh, Chandler, you get behind the desk.
但愿她一进来不会认得你   因为
And when she comes in, hopefully she won't recognize you because...
她怎么会不认得你
Well, why would she?
然后  你对罗斯和我打暗号
Uh, okay. And then you buzz Ross and I.
你是冈萨勒斯先生  我是王先生
You be Mr. Gonzales, and I'll be Mr. Wong.
民族大熔炉
Diverse.
有人叫警卫吗
Anybody call for security?
你们冷静
You be cool.
好  哪位是阿甘中央咖啡厅
Okay. Which one of you guys is Gunther Central Perk?
嘿  乔伊
Hey, Joey.
我的戒指呢  我过世的奶奶的结婚戒指呢  在哪里
Where's my ring? My dead grandmother's wedding ring! Where is it?
你还真冷静
Way to be cool, man.
他在说什么
What's he talking about? Oh!
床头柜的丝绒盒里有只戒指
There was a ring in a box on my nightstand.
你一走  它就不见了
After you left, it was gone.
等等  你们认为我偷了戒指
Wait, you guys think I stole some ring?
对
Yeah.
一定是你偷的  少废话  从实招来
We know you took it! So just save yourself the time and confess.
你们谁啊  少年侦探团吗
Okay, Who are you, the Hardy Boys?
我根本没必要偷什么白痴戒指
I don't need to steal some stupid ring.
我一星期能赚一千六
I make $1,600 a week doing what I do.
你们有人赚那么多吗
Any of you guys make that?
嫁给我
Marry me.
我不懂  戒指整晚都在我房里  如果她没拿
I don't get it. It was in my room all night. If she didn't take it...
我没拿  你没拿  那是谁拿的
...and I didn't take it and you didn't take it. Then who did?
安静  我们在想事情
Shh. We're trying to think.
你怎么会知道是假痛
I still don't get how you know when it's false labor.
你有看到宝宝吗
Well, do you see any babies?
你感觉如何  还好吧  大概
How do you feel? Okay, I guess. I mean...
我不知道
I don't know.
大概是我知道快要结束了
I guess I know it's going to be over soon so...
那不是很好吗
But isn't that a good thing?
你说你受够了  我知道
I mean, you said you were sick of this. I know.
只是一般怀孕完之后
It's just usually, when you're done with the pregnant thing...
就是该当妈妈了
...then you get to do the mom thing.
我却穿着皮裤  喝龙舌兰酒
I'm gonna be, you know, sitting around in my leather pants, drinking tequila.
有些妈妈也会那样
Some moms do that.
那样更悲惨
Yeah, that's even sadder.
我知道这么做的后果
Look, I know what I got myself into, you know?
但他们现在在我肚子里  我好像
It's just that now that they're in me, it's like...
我好像了解他们一样
It's like I know them, you know, and...
把他们送走  我会很难受
It just not gonna be easy when, you know, these little babies have to go away.
我知道
Oh. I know, sweetie.
但你并不会一无所有
But it's not like you're not gonna have anything.
你会有侄子  侄女
I mean, you're gonna have nieces and nephews.
那样  甚至更棒
In some ways, that's even better.
少来  不  是真的
Yeah, okay. No, really.
真的  菲比
Really, Pheebs.
你不必担心他们的大学学费
I mean, you're not gonna be the one worrying about saving for college.
或着他们不乖时骂他们
Or yelling at them when they're bad.
或在他们吵个不停时
You know? Or deciding to put them on Ritalin...
喂他们吃立得宁
...when they just won't calm down.
知道吗
You know?
他们离家出走会来找你
You're gonna be the one they come to when they run away from home.
会找你谈论性的问题
And the one they talk to about sex.
你可以当酷阿姨菲比
You just get to be cool Aunt Phoebe.
酷阿姨菲比
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
我是蛮酷的
I am pretty cool.
还有  你知道吗  天啊  他们一定会爱死你
Yeah, and you know what else? Oh, my God, are they going to love you.
他们会爱死我
They are going to love me. Oh!
谢谢你们  再次感谢
Thanks, you guys. Again. Aw.
喔  不客气
Oh, sweetie.
谢谢  喔  怎么了  天啊
Thanks. Oh! What? Oh, God.
开玩笑的
Just kidding.
怎么了  天哪
Ah! Oh, my God.
又骗到了  你们真好骗
Got you again. You're so easy.
要是他发生什么事  乔伊  兽医说手术很简单
If anything should happen to him... Joey, the vet said it's a simple procedure.
所以呢  搞不好会出错  要是他没撑过来呢
So? Things can go wrong. You don't know. What if he doesn't make it?
他会的  乔伊  要是没有呢
He will, Joe. Yeah, but what if he doesn't?
他是这么乖巧
He's such a good duck.
我好担心他
I'm so worried about him.
有人掉了戒指吗
Somebody lose a ring? Aah!
天哪  谢谢你  谢谢
Oh, my God. Thank you. Thank you so much. Aah!
鸭子怎么样了
How's the duck?
他很好  正在休息  你们可以去见他
He's doing just fine, he's resting now, but you can see him in a little bit.
太好了
Oh. Great.
听着  罗斯  谢谢你这么好的脾气
Oh, hey, listen, Ross, thanks for being so cool about this.
没关系  当然有关系
No, that's all right. No, it's not.
你找我当伴郎  我却让你失望
I mean, you made me your best man and I totally let you down.
少来了  又不是你的错  当然是
Hey, come on. It's not your fault. Yeah, it is.
你就不会弄丢戒指
You wouldn't have lost the ring, right?
知道吗  罗斯  你开始就是对的
You know what? Ross, you were right from the start.
他才应该当你的伴郎  不  应该你当
He should be your best man. No, you should.
别吵了  嘿  嘿
Look, don't argue with me. Hey, hey, hey.
伴郎是我选的
I get to choose my best man.
你们两个我都要
I want both you guys.
真的
Really?
你们都应该陪我站在台前
Both you guys should be up there with me.
你们是我的
I mean, you two are my...
有一个好朋友就
I mean, I'm lucky to have just one good...
谢了
Well, thanks, man.
我去那边看看
I got to go check something, okay?
真孩子气   都够爱哭的
What a baby. Total wuss.